<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mas Cemplon</title>
    <description>Berbagi Informasi Onlien Yang Mendidik</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 17:25:18 +0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 17:25:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Adware is one of many “malwares” or malicious software programs that are unknowingly installed on your computer when you visit online sites and download freebies. When you use share files or visit sites with free downloads of wallpaper, videos, or music, some of these sites will send along adware software with your download.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These malwares are a rapidly growing threat to all computer systems. It is estimated that in the first three months of 2005 over 80% of computer users had some type of malware software program running on their computer, without their knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although it is much less a threat to your computer and information than spyware is, what adware will do is cause pop up banners and advertisements to appear on your computer. These advertisements are displayed on your computer no matter what program you might be using. What the people who place this type of nuisance software on you computer say is that adware advertising helps them to recover costs and allows them to offer you those freebies you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What you want to do to stop adware from appearing on your computer is to first run an anti-adware program. Run this program on demand regularly. Along with an anti-adware software program run your regular computer virus scan on demand also.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check the security level on your computer. You security level setting should be at least medium to help protect you from unwanted downloads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do not download free files from the internet, period. When downloading any software read the end-user license agreement. Some of these agreements will state that when you download their software you are also agreeing to accept a downloaded spyware that may be placed on your computer at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be aware of threats to your computer, and your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THOUSANDS QUALITY but FREE PLR ARTICLES @ www.BuildWebPage.org
You can say thanks for the articles by giving us a link back at http://www.BuildWebPage.org on your links page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 17:25:18 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2021-01-27-What_Is_Adware_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2021-01-27-What_Is_Adware_/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Whiteboards - 24 Square Feet Of Planning Surface To Play With</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dry wipe pens leave marks that can simply be erased using a duster or clean board duster. The pens do leave a powdery residue when the board is wiped clean. Using dry wipe pens is considerably more expensive than chalk, but much less me…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whiteboard, white board, planning system, planning board, home business&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gone are the days of the messy and chalky blackboard, both in the classroom and in conference centers. The blackboard has been replaced by the whiteboard. Users write with dry-wipe pens instead of chalk. The pens come in about eight colors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dry wipe pens leave marks that can simply be erased using a duster or clean board duster. The pens do leave a powdery residue when the board is wiped clean. Using dry wipe pens is considerably more expensive than chalk, but much less messy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whiteboards also make excellent additions to home offices, kitchens and garages. Jot your notes, to do tasks and phone messages on the whiteboard and they will never be lost, as pieces of paper will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A whiteboard will allow you to prioritise all the tasks associated with running a business from home. Planning is made much easier, too. My Internet business revolves around my white-boards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whiteboards come in a wide range of sizes, though the common sizes are 3 feet by 4 feet and 6 feet by 4 feet. Buy the biggest one you can fit on your wall space, because you will manage to fill it much faster than you think. You may have to buy from a specialist office supplier, like Viking Direct, because high street stores are often limited in the stock they carry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interactive whiteboards are another ball game entirely. An interactive board will cost hundreds of dollars, as opposed to a dry wipe plastic board that only has a cost of thirty dollars or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An interactive board allows users to use special non-marking pens that appear to write on the surface, but the board clears when the computer attached to the whiteboard is switched off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interactive board comes into its own when it is used with specially designed software that allows users to project spreadsheets onto the board, then draw on the board with special “pens”, that leave a colored mark on the board, which disappears when the PC is turned off. There is really no mark there at all.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/Whiteboards_-_24_Square_Feet_Of_Planning_Surface_To_Play_With/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Whiteboards_-_24_Square_Feet_Of_Planning_Surface_To_Play_With/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Which is which; Cheap Laptop or Cheap Desktop?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;:
printing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you buy a cheap laptop or a cheap desktop?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may find yourself asking that question many times while shopping for a computer. This guide offers you the pros and cons of owning a laptop versus a desktop pc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Processing speed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Comparing processing speeds, laptops usually lag behind their desktop counterparts. With the rapid advance in microchip technology, the gap between them will become smaller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wireless.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most laptops especially those with Intel mobile chips come with wireless capability out of the box. This means you can get online from any location at home easily without ugly wires if you have a wireless network setup at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Desktop pcs do not typically provide this capability out of the box although that may change in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Memory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Memory chip tends to be more expensive in Laptop than desktop pcs. If you buy a laptop with less than 512MB ram, be prepare to pay more for memory upgrades than you have to with a desktop pc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graphics Display&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of the size of a laptop, most business or entry level laptop use integrated graphics with limited ram. This means most laptops even some expensive ones cannot run graphics intensive applications or 3d games as well as a desktop pc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a desktop pc, you can buy a dedicated graphics card just to serve a graphics intensive application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Portability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Portability is why everyone wants a laptop these days. Because of their size and weight, it is easier to carry a laptop around as opposed to a desktop pc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Screen Display.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone buy laptop for their portability so laptops usually do not come with screens as big as their desktop counterparts. The screen technology used is usually not as good as those used by desktop pc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore with a desktop pc, you can always upgrade to a bigger and better screen whereas for laptop you are stuck with the same screen display for the whole lifespan of the laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So whether you should buy a cheap laptop or a cheap desktop, ask yourself what are your needs? If you want to be able to use a computer wherever you go, then you are looking at a laptop to fulfill your needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However if you do not require the portability of a laptop, play a lot of 3D games, graphic intensive applications, if you care about upgradeability to prolong the lifespan of your investment, then desktop pc is a smarter choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/Which_is_which__Cheap_Laptop_or_Cheap_Desktop_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Which_is_which__Cheap_Laptop_or_Cheap_Desktop_/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where to get hot myspace layouts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Myspace Layouts, Myspace Backgrounds, Myspace Codes, Myspace Graphics&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Myspace is one of the fastest growing sites on the Internet, make sure, they are the hot favorite of visitors. There are an incredible number of features that can be brought on the Myspace account. There are hot favorites as well as those used in a traditional manner. However, it is imperative for the users to go in for pretty layouts that can host a number of features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look for free layouts for the Myspace page using the search engines Google and Yahoo! The search will throw up hundreds of pages. There will be a plenty of options for people to download the layouts. They come in all kinds of styles. All the colors featured in the rainbow and attractive new colors are also included in the layout. Go through the options carefully before downloading and installing the layouts on the account since they are flexible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good way of accessing layouts is to look for the search engines on the Internet. Popular search engines such as Yahoo! and Google drive a lot of Internet traffic for the users. Therefore, the Myspace page should have better features and profiles that can drive more people to the account. The most preferred route to attract more visitors to the site is to have an attractive background to the Myspace web page. The attractive layouts can be designed by the user of Myspace on their own by employing the desktop tools. However, these will be basic layouts and cannot be upgraded to a higher level. Besides, they cannot be changed whenever desired. Once the design of the layout is frozen, altering will take time. However, the updates will be minimal and rich features cannot be added to the layout. Eventually the traffic to the site could be less than the desired level. The best way to ensure that the layout is done in a professional manner is to employ the tools available on the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hot layouts of the Myspace page are available on the Internet. Use the popular search engines such as Google to seek out the layouts. Type the words Myspace layouts in the space provided for search. It will throw up a number of pages that will have links to the layouts of the Myspace page. There are two categories of links. The first category of links provides connectivity to layouts that is available for free. The second category of links provides connectivity to layouts that is licensed. They can be accessed against payment of certain fee. The layouts come in various shapes and colors that can be chosen by the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hot Myspace layouts are in great demand. They are also based on various themes and subjects. Most of the Internet sites offering the hot layouts are updated on a daily basis. The downloading of the hot Myspace layouts is easy. Either you can download the layout as a whole or seek out the codes. The codes are very important while installing the layout. Any mistake could upset the page. Therefore, the codes should be downloaded carefully.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/Where_to_get_hot_myspace_layouts/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Where_to_get_hot_myspace_layouts/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where Are The Dreamers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;dream, dreams, dreamers, john kennedy, bobby kennedy, martin l king, gipper, robert kennedy, teacher, pastor, leader&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the Tennessee Mountain Man was a young man, there were dream girls.  Girls like Liz Taylor, Raquel Welch, Marilyn Monroe, Diana Ross, Nancy Sinatra, Tina Turner and the Vargas girls.  Man, we even thought Dale Evans, Annie Oakley, Miss Kitty, Della Street, and the girl next door were hot… probably a hormone thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there were also dreamers.  Dreamers like John Kennedy who had a dream that challenged and inspired a new generation.  Dreamers like Martin Luther King, Jr. who had a dream that changed a nation.  Bobby Kennedy had a dream.  The Gipper had a dream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then there were the dream makers… dream makers like school teachers who challenged you to be all you could be, professionals like lawyers and doctors who practiced their skills primarily because they cared for their fellow man often for a pound of butter, a dozen fresh farm eggs, a chicken for the dinner table, or a gallon of fresh churned buttermilk, and there were men of God who spread the Gospel out of love for something other than numbers, pride and money.  There were local community leaders who inspired and they actually got out on the street and interacted with their citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The poet Langston Hughes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hold fast to dreams&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For if dreams die&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is a broken-winged bird&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That cannot fly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hold fast to dreams&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For when dreams go&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is a barren field&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frozen with snow.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where are the Dr Kildare’s that dare challenge one to a noble service bigger than themselves rather than seeking self aggrandizement? 
Where is America’s future?  Where are all the dream inspiring TV shows and actual road trips like Route 66?  Where are real cars that people can fall in love with?  Where are all the road side stands where a child’s imagination could be driven for hours without anything being stolen or broken?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where have all the dreamers gone?  Where have the dream makers gone?  Why are those who started with nothing but a dream now setting comfortably in their million dollar homes sipping brandy in the evening and ensconced in their ivory towers by day while dreamers disappear from the landscape?  Who do they think will inspire a new generation to dream, to dare if they don’t?  What we have been given, what we have accomplished comes with a price which cannot be abdicated.  The dream, the inspiration must be passed to a new generation.  They must strive for a new frontier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, community pride, community love, community care, 4-H Clubs, Boy Scouts, FFA, school plays and cake walks where art thou?  The Computerman don’t see his grandchildren pursuing any of these things or dreaming about what could be.  We have not arrived by a long shot.  Where is the next generation and what will it accomplish?  Will it add anything worthwhile to God’s earth or be self absorbed or be couch potatoes playing with the latest gizmo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does your pastor inspire the young people, or is he or she just there to count heads and collect dollars?  If it is not the former, it is time for a new pastor.  Do the teachers in your schools inspire and motivate students?  If not, send them packing.  Their grossly extended vacation schedule and short hours be damned.  Let them do that for which they are best suited like slinging burgers at the Golden Arches rather than holding back our prodigy.  Do civic and political leaders lead?  If not, replace them, and the sooner the better for the next generation of dreamers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is hanging in the hood so popular today?  Why are gangs and gang bangers so prevalent?  Why can’t our children dream beyond their current circumstances?  We did!  We wanted to be Wyatt Earp (at least the TV image), Matt Dillon, The Lawman, Perry Mason, Dr Marcus Welby, M.D., Paladin, Pat Garrett or perhaps even the Reverend Billy Graham or the next Reverend Dr Martin Luther King or a Sister Theresa or maybe Elvis or Ricky Nelson and we enjoyed watching Lassie while wolfing down a big bowl of pop corn or home parched peanuts while we dreamed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had to dream before we acted, before we accomplished. Before we had the answers there were the dreams. There was a dream, then there was Rosa Parks.  There was a dream, then there was John Glenn!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We dreamed… we dreamed of being… we dreamed of becoming… we dreamed of serving… we dreamed of living… we dreamed of loving… we dreamed of giving…  We dreamed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the theater of our minds we slipped the surly bonds of earth and dared ponder the possibilities that lay before us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What happened?  Where have all the dreamers gone?  Are today’s sick, addicted, anorexic pop stars tomorrows future?  Where are the dream makers?  Who can capture the imagination and propel it forward through the haze of uncertainty and through the unknown into a better brighter tomorrow? Who?  Where are the dream makers?!  Where are the dreamers?!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/Where_Are_The_Dreamers/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Where_Are_The_Dreamers/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When To Rent A Laptop Computer </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are a few reasons to rent a laptop computer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If you need technology on short notice or for a short time, it is best to rent a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If you need a large quantity of laptop computers for a training class, it is best to rent laptops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If your laptop computers are on back order but your staff isn’t, it’s best to rent laptops for imm…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;laptop rental,notebook rental,computer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most companies either lease or buy their computer equipment, but why or when should a company rent laptop or notebook computers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few reasons to rent a laptop computer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If you need technology on short notice or for a short time, it is best to rent a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If you need a large quantity of laptop computers for a training class, it is best to rent laptops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If your laptop computers are on back order but your staff isn’t, it’s best to rent laptops for immediate installation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-If you need a wireless laptop computers for travel and all your company laptops and notebook computers are wired.
People confuse computer renting with leasing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renting is short term in nature and is very flexible. Leasing, like buying is a fixed arrangement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can extend the rental or cancel at any time with no penalty. Leases can’t be cancelled without a ‘severe penalty’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Renting laptops is totally flexible, requires no capital budget and can often be accomplished with a company credit card. For most companies, renting is as easy as getting office supplies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rental companies have expert computer technicians who deliver, install and test your laptop rental right at your office, training room, trade show booth, seminar, convention or conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rental companies have everything you need and a backup plan if something unexpected happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other reasons why businesses rent laptop computers include temporary offices, traveling executives and temporary employees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temporary Offices
Temporary offices can be made complete with rental laptop computers, printers, copiers and fax machines. The hardware will be configured to your company specifications and installed at any remote location in the United States or Canada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rentacomputer.com has set up temporary offices in hotel rooms, trailers, warehouses and convention centers. Temporary offices have been set up for State and Federal Government agencies such as FEMA, the FBI and the IRS. Also legal firms, television networks covering hurricane disasters, movie studios setting up “on location”, and new building construction sites, corporate mergers and takeovers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traveling Executives
Traveling executives won’t have to carry portable laptop computers through airports or other public transportation facilities. Executives can have technology, preconfigured and tested, waiting at their final destination! Traveling with technology is one hassle that can be easily avoided by calling a computer rental expert like a Temporary Technology Travel Agent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temporary Employees
Temporary employees need temporary technology. By renting laptop computers you can coordinate the installation and removal of computers, printers and other technology for any period of time specified. If you hire temporary employees, hire temporary technology too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next time you have a temporary or special need, consider renting laptop computer technology and technical expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THOUSANDS QUALITY but FREE PLR ARTICLES @ www.BuildWebPage.org
You can say thanks for the articles by giving us a link back at http://www.BuildWebPage.org on your links page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/When_To_Rent_A_Laptop_Computer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/When_To_Rent_A_Laptop_Computer/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>When Is Professional Computer Repair Advisable?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some computer repairs are difficult for the average person to do without causing damage to their computer or a peripheral. There are some repairs I’d classify as beginner level, some as …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;computer repair school,computer repair training,pc repair school,pc repair training&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many computer repairs that the average person can perform without much problem. Things like installing CD-ROM drives, sound cards and other expansion cards don’t take much computer knowledge. How can you know though when you are over your head and need professional computer help?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some computer repairs are difficult for the average person to do without causing damage to their computer or a peripheral. There are some repairs I’d classify as beginner level, some as intermediate and others as advanced. I’ve already mentioned some repairs I would call beginner level. Some intermediate repairs include replacing your hard drive and installing an operating system. There was a time when something like this was advanced but with modern Microsoft operating systems like Windows XP and Windows Vista, operating system installations are not as advanced as they used to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what repairs should a beginner not attempt? I would suggest some things like replacing your motherboard. The need to replace your motherboard can come either when you are ready to upgrade your motherboard to something newer or when your computer case power supply kicks the bucket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another repair I would caution against is based in software. That’s when you need to clean out a nasty virus or spyware program. It is very easy to cause you much grief if you don’t do it right. You could lose access to the data on your hard drive if you mess up your operating system. Now if you don’t care about the data on your hard drive, simply re-installing your operating system while making sure to format your hard drive can usually solve a software problem. Kind of like killing a fly with a large shovel. It works but it is overkill. A professional computer repair technician can help you keep your data while ridding you of a virus infection.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/When_Is_Professional_Computer_Repair_Advisable_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/When_Is_Professional_Computer_Repair_Advisable_/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What's It Going To Be?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;coupon, dell coupon, grocery coupon, online coupon, coupon code, free coupon, printable coupon, office depot coupon, old navy coupon, jc penney coupon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computers are one of the most interesting and complex machines on the planet. They have the ability to intrigue anyone who sits down and attempts to use it. On the other hand though, they also have the ability to confuse the heck out of you! When  I think about computers, I think about the internet, Microsoft Word (for school), and games. What sort of computer I buy should be user friendly in all three of these aspects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First you have to make a big decision… Apple or Windows. They both have great features, and are both more user friendly for each individule user. Windows is compatible with several computer manufacturers, including HP Pavilion, Compaq, and Dell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, in my case, I need to take a close look at each option, as I have specific uses for my machine. When purchasing a computer you should be aware of what your main purpose with it is. For some it is business, others gaming, and for many, it is used for school. Make sure you test each version, Apple and Windows. If Apple seems the most compatible with your purpose, then congradulations! Your choice is made. But if you decide Apple is not right for you, take a look at all the operating systems that there is for Windows. There are several, each with different features, and you should choose the one that is right for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, the purchase of a computer is not always black and white. What’s it going to be for you?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/What_s_It_Going_To_Be_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/What_s_It_Going_To_Be_/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is eSATA?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;eSATA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eSATA is an example of an extension to current serial ATA standards. The main function of eSATA is to make it possible for SATA drives to be attached externally, creating a wider network of functionality by combining the power of each of the drives.  Relatively new, eSATA means that it is possible to engage in data transfer and processing much more quickly than with traditional methods of connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Does eSATA Work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basic idea behind eSATA is make it possible to connect multiple drives without having to employ cables or wired connections of some sort. Traditional methods of connecting the external hard drives relied upon the use of such devices as FireWire or USB cables. eSATA does away with all that and makes it possible to connected several external drives in a very short period of time, without all the work of figuring out which cable will do the job. ESATA is based on established standards and will work every time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Are Some of the Advantages of eSATA?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the immediate advantages of using eSATA is that the eSATA cables are usually longer and easier to distinguish from the jumble of wiring that is used to connect various devices. Anyone who operates even a home system knows how easy it is for wires and cables to become snared as they run across one another and make it virtually impossible to tell what runs where. eSATA cables are generally at least six feet long and tend to be somewhat different in appearance than USB cables and FireWire. One glance at the cable and you know what it is and where it goes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another advantage is the ease of connecting and disconnecting the external drive. ESATA drives are designed with what are known as hot plugs. This means the cables can be connected and disconnected with ease, and without the need to power down the system in order to add or remove a drive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Along with the esthetics, eSATA also helps to provide excellent rates of data transfer that are sometimes better than can be achieved with a USB connection. There are currently versions of eSATA on the market that will provide data transfer speeds of between 150MBps to 300 MBps. That is a great deal of power when it comes to using an external drive, and is generally much better than can be achieved using a USB cable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THOUSANDS QUALITY but FREE PLR ARTICLES @ www.BuildWebPage.org
You can say thanks for the articles by giving us a link back at http://www.BuildWebPage.org on your links page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/What_is_eSATA_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/What_is_eSATA_/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is dBm?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;dBm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes identified as dBmW, dBm has to do with the degree of power measured in decibels as it relates to one millwatt. The calculation of dBm is helpful in several different types of applications, and can be used to calculate any size power ratio. In most cases, dBm is used to measure absolute power in a given setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Types of Systems Make Use of dBm?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three basic types of networks will make use of a dBm calculation on a regular basis. Radio, microwave, and fiber optic networks all employ the use of dBm. In each case, the measurement helps to ensure that the amount of wattage employed by the network remains within proscribed limits, but is sufficient to generate the energy required for operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Is dBm Calculated?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is important to note that dBm is referenced to the watt. This means that dBm represents an absolute unit, which is essential to the task of defining absolute power. Essentially, a zero dBm is the equivalent of one milliwatt. This means that in the event of the occurrence of 3 milliwatts, the dBm would come to 4. If the millwatts were less than one, such as a half millwatt, that would make the dBm roughly a -3, since the power is reduced by half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Widespread is the use of dBm as a Calculation?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The use of dBm is common in the United States, where unweighted measurement is employed in many different applications. This is especially true when it is necessary to ascertain the wattage involved in order to maintain transmissions within a certain bandwidth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do Consumers Make Use of dBm?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While consumers tend to reap the rewards of the use of dBm by various networks that deliver signaling, the average consumer has no real need for the use of dBm. The measurement tool is mainly used by professionals who are responsible for maintaining proper bandwidth in accordance with federal regulations and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, it must be noted that just about every consumer will benefit from the use of dBm in some way. Everything from telephone calls to bandwidth on home computers, radio to television broadcasts, and a number of other related transmissions are monitored and measured with the use of dBm.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <link>/What_is_dBm_/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/What_is_dBm_/</guid>
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        
        <category>Computers</category>
        
        <category>Technology</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
